(Howard:)-She nailed it.
-Sounds about right.
(Leonard:)But, you forget,
I did ask you out in real life.
(Amy:)Which couldn't have happened
if you didn't live across the hall from her
(Amy:)which couldn't have
happened without Sheldon.
(Amy:)Same goes with you guys.
(Amy:)If Leonard wasn't with Penny,
(Amy:)she never would have set you up.
(Howard:)Doesn't matter.
Bernadette still would've been working
(Howard:)at The Cheesecake Factory,
(Howard:)and I still would've been
working this beefcake factory.
(Howard:)You would've been all over me.
(Amy:)Well....
(Bernadette:)Hey, Penny, can I take that table?
(Penny:)Sure, why?
(Bernadette:)The one in the turtleneck is cute.
(Raj:)Open wide,
here comes the happy train.
(Howard:)Mm-HM...
Chug-a chug-a, yum, yum.
(Raj:)Hang on.
(Raj:)You got a...
You got a little something.
(Bernadette:)Never mind.